<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.klettres.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KBokstavar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Klettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKLettresxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KLettres</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">語言_KLetters</name>
  <summary>Learn The Alphabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Naučite abecedu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Aprendre l'alfabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aprendre l'alfabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Výuka abecedy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Lerne das Alphabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Μάθετε την Αλφαβήτα</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Learn The Alphabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Aprende el alfabeto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Tähestiku õppimine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Alfabetoa ikasi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Opi aakkoset</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Apprenez l'alphabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Aprende o alfabeto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Tanulja meg az ABC-t</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Mempelajari Alfabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Impara l'alfabeto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">알파벳 익히기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Dat Alfabeet lehren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Leer het alfabet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Lær alfabetet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Nauka alfabetu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Aprender o Alfabeto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Aprenda o alfabeto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Изучение алфавита</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Výuka abecedy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Naučite se abecedo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Inlärning av alfabetet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Alfabeyi Öğrenin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Вивчення абетки</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxLearn The Alphabetxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">学习字母</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">語言_KLetters</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KLettres is an application specially designed to help the user to learn an alphabet in a new language and then to learn to read simple syllables. The user can be a young child aged from two and a half or an adult that wants to learn the basics of a foreign language. There are currently 25 languages available: Arabian, Brazilian Portuguese, Czech, Danish, Dutch, British English, US English, Phonics English, French, German, Hebrew, Hungarian, Italian, Kannada, Low Saxon, Malayalam, Norwegian Bokmål, Punjabi, Luganda, Romanized Hindi, Russian, Spanish, Slovak, Telugu and Ukrainian. KLettres provides a special user interface and themes for younger users.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">KLettres je aplikacija specijalno dizajnirana da pomogne korisniku da uči alfabetu u novom jeziku, a zatim da nauči da čita jednostavne slogove. Korisnik može biti dijete uzrasta od dvije i po ili odrasla osoba koja želi da nauči osnove stranog jezika. Trenutno ima 25 jezika dostupnih: arapski, brazilski portugalski, češki, danski, holandski, britanski engleski, američki engleski, fonetski engleski, francuski, nemački, hebrejski, mađarski, italijanski, kanada, Lov Sakon, malajalam, norveški bokmal, pandžabi, Luganda , romanizovanimhindi, ruski, španski, slovački, ukrajinski i telugu. KLettres daje poseban korisnički interfejs i teme za mlađe korisnike.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KLettres és una aplicació especialment dissenyada per a ajudar a l'usuari a aprendre un alfabet en un idioma nou i després a prendre a llegir síl·labes senzilles. L'usuari pot ser des d'un infant de dos anys i mig a un adult que vol aprendre les bases d'un idioma estranger. Actualment hi ha 25 idiomes disponibles: àrab, portuguès de Brasil, txec, danès, neerlandès, anglès britànic, anglès dels EUA, anglès fònic, francès, alemany, hebreu, hongarès, italià, kanarès, baix saxó, malaiàlam, noruec Bokmal, panjabi, luganda, hindi romanitzat, rus, espanyol, eslovac, telugu i ucraïnès. El KLettres proporciona una interfície d'usuari espacial i temes per a usuaris joves.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KLettres és una aplicació especialment dissenyada per a ajudar a l'usuari a aprendre un alfabet en un idioma nou i després a prendre a llegir síl·labes senzilles. L'usuari pot ser des d'un infant de dos anys i mig a un adult que vol aprendre les bases d'un idioma estranger. Actualment hi ha 25 idiomes disponibles: àrab, portugués de Brasil, txec, danés, neerlandés, anglés britànic, anglés dels EUA, anglés fònic, francés, alemany, hebreu, hongarés, italià, kanarés, baix saxó, malaiàlam, noruec Bokmal, panjabi, luganda, hindi romanitzat, rus, espanyol, eslovac, telugu i ucraïnés. El KLettres proporciona una interfície d'usuari espacial i temes per a usuaris joves.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KLettres ist eine Anwendung, die dafür erstellt wurde, dem Benutzer das Lernen des Alphabets in einer neuen Sprache zu erleichtern und dann anschließend das Lesen von einfachen Silben. Der Benutzer kann ein junges Kind von zweieinhalb sein oder ein Erwachsener, der die Grundlage einer fremden Sprache lernen möchte.Fünfundzwanzig Sprachen sind zurzeit verfügbar: Arabisch, Brasilianisches Portugiesisch, Tschechisch, Dänisch, Holländisch, Britisches Englisch, Amerikanisches Englisch, Englisches Phonics, Französisch, Deutsch, Hebräisch, Ungarisch, Italienisch, Kanadisch, Niederdeutsch, Malayam, Norwegisch Bokmål, Punjab, Hindi (in lateinischer Umschrift), Russisch, Spanisch, Slowakisch, Telugu und Ukrainisch. KLettres hat eine Benutzeroberfläche und Designs speziell für junge Benutzer. </p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KLettres είναι μία εφαρμογή ειδικά σχεδιασμένη για να βοηθήσει τον χρήστη να μάθει ένα αλφάβητο σε μια νέα γλώσσα και έπειτα να μπορεί να διαβάζει απλές συλλαβές. Ο χρήστης μπορέι να είναι ένα νήπιο ηλικίας από δυόμισι ετών ή ένας ενήλικας που θέλει να μάθει τα βασικά μιας ξένης γλώσσας. Προς το παρόν υπάρχουν διαθέσιμες 25 γλώσσες: Αραβικά, Πορτογαλικά της Βραζιλίας, Τσεχικά, Δανικά, Ολλανδικά, Αγγλικά Βρετανίας, Αγγλικά Ηνωμένων Πολιτειών, Αγγλική φωνολογία, Γαλλικά, Γερμανικά, Εβραϊκά, Ουγγαρέζικα, Ιταλικά, Κανάντα, Κάτω Σαξωνίας, Μαλαγιαλάμ, Νορβηγικά Μποκμάλ, Παντζάμπι, Λουγκάντα, Χίντι Λατινικής γραφής, Ρωσικά, Ισπανικά, Σλοβακικά, Τελούγκου και Ουκρανικά. Το KLettres περιλαμβάνει ένα ειδικό περιβάλλον χρήσης και θέματ αγια χρήστες νεαρής ηλικίας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KLettres is an application specially designed to help the user to learn an alphabet in a new language and then to learn to read simple syllables. The user can be a young child aged from two and a half or an adult that wants to learn the basics of a foreign language. There are currently 25 languages available: Arabian, Brazilian Portuguese, Czech, Danish, Dutch, British English, US English, Phonics English, French, German, Hebrew, Hungarian, Italian, Kannada, Low Saxon, Malayalam, Norwegian Bokmål, Punjabi, Luganda, Romanized Hindi, Russian, Spanish, Slovak, Telugu and Ukrainian. KLettres provides a special user interface and themes for younger users.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KLettres es una aplicación especialmente diseñada para ayudar al usuario a aprender un alfabeto en otro idioma y después, a aprender a leer sílabas sencillas. El usuario puede ser un niño de a partir de dos años o un adulto que quiere aprender la base de un idioma extranjero. Actualmente, hay 25 idiomas disponibles: árabe, brasileño, portugués, checo, danés, holandés, inglés británico, inglés de Estados Unidos, ingles fónico, francés, alemán, hebreo, húngaro, italiano, kannada, bajo sajón, malayo, bokmål noruego, punjabí, luganda, hindi romanizado, ruso, español, eslovaco, telugú y ucraniano. KLettres proporciona una interfaz de usuario y temas especiales para los usuarios más jóvenes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KLettres on rakendus, mille eesmärk on aidata õppuril omandada uue keele tähestik ja seejärel lugeda lihtsamaid silpe. Õppur võib olla väike laps (alates umbes 2.5-aastastest) või ka täiskasvanu, kes soovib tundma õppida mõne võõrkeele põhitõdesid. Praegu on välja pakkuda 25 keelt: alamsaksa, araabia, Brasiilia portugali, Briti inglise, foneetiline inglise, heebrea, hispaania, hollandi, itaalia, kannada, latiniseeritud hindi, luganda, malajalami, Norra Bokmåli, pandžaabi, prantsuse, saksa, slovaki, taani, telugu, tšehhi, ukraina, ungari, USA inglise ja vene keel. KLettres pakub eriti noortele õppuritele spetsiaalset kasutajaliidest ja teemasid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KLettres erabiltzaileari hizkuntza berri bateko alfabetoa ikasten laguntzeko, eta ondoren silaba sinpleak irakurtzen laguntzeko, bereziki diseinatutako aplikazio bat da. Erabiltzailea bi urte eta erditik aurrerako haur gazte bat edo atzerriko hizkuntza baten oinarrizkoa  ikasi nahi duen heldu bat izan daiteke. Gaur egun 25 hizkuntza daude erabilgarri: AEBko ingelesa, alemana, arabiera, behe saxoniera, Brasileko portugesa, Britainiako ingelesa, daniera, errusiera, eslovakiera, frantsesa, gaztelania, hebreera, hindi erromanikoa, hungariera, italiera, ingeles fonikoa, kannada, luganda, malabarera, nederlandera, norvegiera Bokmål, punjabera, telugu, txekiera eta ukrainera. KLettres-ek erabiltzaile interfaze bat eta gai bereziak eskaintzen ditu erabiltzaile gazteagoentzat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KLettres on sovellus, joka on suunniteltu erityisesti auttamaan käyttäjää oppimaan uuden kielen aakkoset ja oppimaan sitten lukemaan yksinkertaisia tavuja. Käyttäjä voi olla kaksi ja puoli -vuotiaasta lapsesta aikuiseen, joka haluaa oppia vieraan kielen perusteet. Tällä hetkellä on saatavilla 25 kieltä: alasaksa, amerikanenglanti, arabia, brasilianportugali, brittienglanti, englannin äänteet, espanja, ganda, heprea, hollanti, italia, kannada, latinaistettu hindi, malajalam, norjan bokmål, pandžabi, ranska, saksa, slovakki, tanska, telugu, tšekki, ukraina, unkari ja venäjä. KLettresissä on nuorempia käyttäjiä varten oma käyttöliittymä ja teemoja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KLettres est une application spécialement conçue pour aider l'utilisateur à apprendre l'alphabet d'une nouvelle langue puis l'aider à apprendre à lire des syllabes simples. L'utilisateur peut être un jeune enfant à partir de deux ans et demi ou un adulte qui souhaite apprendre les rudiments d'une langue étrangère. 25 langues sont disponibles : arabe, portugais brésilien, tchèque, danois, néerlandais, anglais britannique, anglais américain, anglais phonétique, français, allemand, hébreu, hongrois, italien, kannada, bas saxon, malayalam, norvégien bokmål, pendjabi, luganda, hindi romanisé, russe, espagnol, slovaque, télougou et ukrainien. KLettres fournit une interface utilisateur spéciale et des thèmes pour les jeunes utilisateurs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KLettres é unha aplicación deseñado especialmente para axudar aos usuarios a aprender o alfabeto nun novo idioma e aprender a continuación a ler sílabas sinxelas. O usuario pode ser por exemplo un rapaz de dous anos e medio ou un adulto que quere aprender a base dun idioma estranxeiro. Actualmente hai 25 idiomas dispoñíbeis: alemán, árabe, baixo saxón, bokmål, canarés, castelán, checo, danés, eslovaco, francés, hebreo, hindi romanizado, holandés, húngaro, inglés británico, inglés estadounidense, inglés silábico, italiano, luganda, malaialam, portugués do Brasil, punjabi, ruso, telugu e ucraíno. KLettres fornece unha interface de usuario e temas especiais para rapaces.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KLettres adalah aplikasi yang dirancang khusus untuk membantu pengguna mempelajari alfabet dalam bahasa baru dan kemudian belajar membaca suku kata sederhana. Pengguna dapat berupa anak kecil berusia dua setengah tahun atau orang dewasa yang ingin mempelajari dasar-dasar bahasa asing. Saat ini ada 25 bahasa yang tersedia: Arab, Portugis Brasil, Ceko, Denmark, Belanda, Inggris British, Inggris US, Inggris Phonics, Prancis, Jerman, Ibrani, Hongaria, Italia, Kannada, Low Saxon, Malayalam, Bokmål Norwegia, Punjabi, Luganda , Hindi, Rusia, Spanyol, Slovakia, Telugu dan Ukraina. KLettres menyediakan antarmuka dan tema pengguna khusus untuk pengguna yang lebih muda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KLettres è un'applicazione progettata specificatamente per aiutare gli utenti ad imparare l'alfabeto di una nuova lingua e quindi a leggere semplici sillabe. L'utente può essere un bambino dai due anni e mezzo in su oppure un adulto che vuole imparare le basi di una lingua straniera. Al momento sono supportate 25 lingue: arabo, portoghese del Brasile, ceco, danese, olandese, inglese britannico, inglese americano, inglese fonetico, francese, tedesco, ebraico, ungherese, italiano, kannada, basso sassone, malese, norvegese bokmål, punjabi, luganda, hindi romanizzato, russo, spagnolo, slovacco, telugu e ucraino.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KLettres는 새 언어의 글자를 익히고 간단한 음절을 읽는 법을 연습하는 도구입니다. 2세 어린이부터 외국어를 배우려는 성인까지 모든 학습자에게 어울립니다. 현재 다음 25개 언어를 지원합니다: 네덜란드어, 노르웨이어 보크몰, 덴마크어, 독일어, 러시아어, 루간다어, 말라얄람어, 미국 영어, 브라질 포르투갈어, 스페인어, 슬로바키아어, 아랍어, 영국 영어, 우크라이나어, 이탈리아어, 저지 독일, 체코어, 칸나다어, 텔루구어, 파닉스 영어, 펀자브어, 프랑스어, 헝가리어, 히브리어, 힌디어(로마자). KLettres는 어린이용 사용자 인터페이스와 테마를 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">KLettres is en Programm, dat Brukers hölpt, dat Alfabet in en nieg Spraak to lehren un denn ok eenfach Sülven in disse Spraak to lesen. De Bruker kann en lütt Blaag vun tweeenhalf Johr oder en Opwussen wesen, de dat Grundweten vun en nieg Spraak lehren will. Opstunns sünd 25 Spraken verföögbor: Araabsch, Brasiliaansch Portugeesch, Tschechsch, Däänsch, Nedderlannsch, Britsch Engelsch, US Engelsch, Foneetsch Engelsch, Franzöösch, Hoochdüütsch, Hebrääsch, Ungaarsch, Italieensch, Kannadaansch, Plattdüütsch, Malayalaamsch, Norweegsch (Bokmål), Pandschaabsch, Lugandsch, Romaniseert Hindi, Russ'sch, Spaansch, Slowaaksch, Telugu un Ukrainsch. KLetrres hett en besünner Böversiet un Mustern för jünger Brukers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KLettres is een toepassing speciaal ontworpen om de gebruiker te helpen bij het leren van het alfabet van een nieuwe taal en daarna het leren lezen van eenvoudige zinnen. De gebruiker kan een jong kind zijn in de leeftijd van twee en een half of een volwassene die de basis van een vreemde taal wil leren. Er zijn nu 25 talen beschikbaar: Arabisch, Braziliaans Portugees, Tsjechisch, Deens, Nederlands, Brits Engels, VS Engels, Fonetisch Engels, Frans, Duits, Hebreeuws, Hongaars, Italiaans, Kannada, Nedersaksisch, Malayalam, Noors Bokmål, Punjabi, Luganda, Geromaniseerd Hindi, Russisch, Spaans, Slowaaks, Telugu en Oekraïens. KLettres biedt een speciaal gebruikersinterface en thema's voor jonge gebruikers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KLettres er eit program du kan bruka til å læra alfabetet i ulike språk og så læra å lesa enkle stavingar. Programmet passar både for ungar frå to eit halvt år og oppover og for å vaksne som vil få i lita innføring i eit nytt språk. Det er 25 støtta språk: arabisk, Brasil-portugisisk, dansk, engelsk (britisk, amerikansk og fonetisk), fransk, hebraisk, italiensk, kannada, luganda, malayalam, nederlandsk, norsk (bokmål), punjabi, romanisert hindi, russisk, slovakisk, spansk, telugu, tsjekkisk, tysk, ukrainsk og ungarsk. For dei yngste har programmet ei tilpassa brukarflate og eit eige tema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KLettres jest programem specjalnie zaprojektowanym do pomocy użytkownikowi przy nauce alfabetu w nowym języku, a następnie do nauki prostych sylab. Użytkownik może być małym dzieckiem w wieku dwóch i pół roku lub dorosłym, który chce się nauczyć podstaw obcego języka. Dostępnych jest dwadzieścia języków: Arabski, Czeski, Portugalski Brazylijski, Angielski Brytyjski, Duński, Holenderski, Angielski, Francuski, Niemiecki, Hebrajski, Węgierski, Włoski, Kanadyjski, Dolno saksoński, Luganda, Malayalam, Zromanizowany Hindi, Hiszpański, Słowacki, Telugu i Ukraiński. KLettres zapewnia własny układ sterowania programem i wystroje dla młodszych użytkowników.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KLettres é uma aplicação desenhada especialmente para ajudar o utilizador a aprender o alfabeto numa nova língua e de depois aprender a ler sílabas simples. O utilizador poderá ser desde uma criança de dois anos até um adulto que deseje aprender as bases de uma língua estrangeira. Estão disponíveis de momento 25 línguas: Árabe, Português do Brasil, Checo, Dinamarquês, Holandês, Inglês Britânico, Inglês dos EUA, Inglês Fonético, Francês, Alemão, Hebraico, Húngaro, Italiano, Kannada, Baixo-Saxão, Malayalam, Norueguês Bokmål, Punjabi, Luganda, Hindu Romanizado, Russo, Espanhol, Eslovaco, Telugu e Ucraniano. O KLettres oferece uma interface de utilizador e temas especiais para os utilizadores mais novos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KLettres é um aplicativo especialmente desenvolvido para ajudar o usuário a aprender o alfabeto de um novo idioma e depois aprender a ler sílabas simples. O usuário pode ser uma criança de idade reduzida, a partir de dois anos e meio, até um adulto que só queira aprender as bases de um idioma estrangeiro. Existem 25 idiomas disponíveis: Árabe, Português do Brasil, Tcheco, Dinamarquês, Holandês, Inglês Britânico, Inglês dos EUA, Fonética de Inglês, Francês, Alemão, Hebraico, Húngaro, Italiano, Canarês, Baixo-Saxão, Malaiala, Norueguês, Panjabi, Luganda, Hindi Romanizado, Russo, Espanhol, Eslovaco, Telugu e Ucraniano. O KLettres oferece uma interface de usuário especial e temas infantis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KLettres je aplikácia špeciálne určená na pomoc pri výuke abecedy v novom jazyku a potom na naučenie čítania jednoduchých slabík. Používateľ môže byť malé dieťa od 2 a pol roka alebo dospelý, ktorý sa chce naučiť základy cudzieho jazyka. Aktuálne je dostupných 25 jazykov: arabčina, brazílska portugalčina, čeština, dánčina, holandčina, britská angličtina, americká angličtina, fonetická angličtina, francúzština, nemčina, hebrejčina, maďarčina, taliančina, kannadčina, dolná saština, malajalamčina, nórčina Bokmål, pandžábčina, lugandčina, romanizovaná hindčina, ruština, španielčina, slovenčina, telugčina a ukrajinčina. KLettres má špeciálne používateľské prostredie a témy pre mladších používateľov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KLettres je program, ki je bil zasnovan tako, da pomaga uporabniku pri učenju abecede njemu neznanega jezika in ga tudi nauči kako prebrati preproste zloge. Uporabnik je lahko otrok starejši od dveh let ali pa odrasli, ki se želi naučiti osnov tujega jezika. Trenutno je na voljo 25 jezikov: arabščina, brazilska portugalščina, češčina, danščina, nizozemščina, britanska angleščina, angleščina ZDA, fonetična angleščina, francoščina, nemščina, hebrejščina, madžarščina, italijanščina, kannadščina, spodnjesaščina, malajalamščina, knjižna norveščina, pandžabščina, jezik Luganda, Romanizirani hindi, ruščina, španščina, slovaščina, teluščina in ukrajinščina. KLettres za mlajše uporabnike ponuja poseben uporabniški vmesnik in teme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Klettres är ett program som är särskilt framtaget för att hjälpa användaren att lära sig alfabetet på ett nytt språk och sedan lära sig läsa enkla stavelser. Användaren kan vara ett litet barn från två och ett halvt år, eller en vuxen som vill lära sig grunderna i ett främmande språk. För närvarande är 25 språk är tillgängliga: amerikansk engelska, arabiska, brasiliansk portugisiska, brittisk engelska, danska, franska, hebreiska, holländska, italienska, kanaresiska, luganda, lågsaxiska, malayalam, norskt bokmål, phonics engelska, punjabi, romansk hindi, ryska, slovakiska, spanska, telugu, tjeckiska, tyska, ukrainska och ungerska.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KLettres kullanıcıların yeni bir dilin alfabesini ve daha sonra basit heceleri okumayı öğrenmeleri için tasarlanmış bir uygulamadır. Kullanıcı iki buçuk yaşındaki bir çocuktan yeni bir yabancı dilin temellerini öğrenmek isteyen bir yetişkine kadar herkes olabilir. Halen 25 farklı dil desteklenmektedir: Arapça, Brezilya Portekizcesi, Çekçe, Danca, Hollandaca, İngiliz İngilizcesi, Amerikan İngilizcesi, Konuşma İngilizcesi, Fransızca, Almanca, İbranice, Macarca, İtalyanca, Kannada Dili, Aşağı Saksonca, Malayalam Dili, Norveççe, Pencap Dili, Luganda Dili, Şapkalı Hintçe, Rusça, İspanyolca, Slovakça, Telugu Dili ve Ukraynaca. KLettres daha küçük kullanıcılar için özel bir arayüz ve tema sunmaktadır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KLettres — це програма, спеціально розроблена для того, щоб допомогти користувачеві вивчити абетку нової мови, а потім навчитися читати прості склади. Користувачем може бути як дитина віком від двох з половиною років, так і доросла людина, яка бажає вивчити основи іноземної мови. У поточній версії ви можете скористатися такими двадцятьма п’ятьма мовами: арабська, бразильська португальська, чеська, данська, голландська, британська англійська, американська англійська, фонетична англійська, французька, німецька, іврит, угорська, італійська, каннада, нижньосаксонська, луганда, малаялам, латинізована гінді, іспанська, російська,словацька, телугу та українська.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKLettres is an application specially designed to help the user to learn an alphabet in a new language and then to learn to read simple syllables. The user can be a young child aged from two and a half or an adult that wants to learn the basics of a foreign language. There are currently 25 languages available: Arabian, Brazilian Portuguese, Czech, Danish, Dutch, British English, US English, Phonics English, French, German, Hebrew, Hungarian, Italian, Kannada, Low Saxon, Malayalam, Norwegian Bokmål, Punjabi, Luganda, Romanized Hindi, Russian, Spanish, Slovak, Telugu and Ukrainian. KLettres provides a special user interface and themes for younger users.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KLettres 是一套特別設計協助使用者學習新語言的字母，並且學會讀簡單音節的應用程式。使用者可以是兩歲半的孩子，或是想學新外語的成人。目前有包括阿拉伯語、巴西葡萄牙語、捷克語、丹麥語、荷蘭語、英式英語、美式英語等等 25 種語言。KLettres 針對小小孩也提供了一套特別的使用者介面。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://edu.kde.org/klettres/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=klettres</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=klettres</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=klettres&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>KLettres training session</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Sessió d'entrenament del KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Sessió d'entrenament del KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Übungssitzung in KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Συνεδρία εξάσκησης KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">KLettres training session</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Sesión de entrenamiento de KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">KLettresi harjutusseanss</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">KLettres trebakuntza saioa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Séance d'entraînement sur KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Sesión de adestramento de KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Sesi pembelajaran KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Sessione di apprendimento in KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KLettres 연습 세션</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Trainingsessie van KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Læreøkt i KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Sesja ćwiczeń z KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Sessão de exercício do KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Sessão de treinamento do KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Školenie KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Vaje branja s KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Övningssession i Klettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Навчальний сеанс KLettres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxKLettres training sessionxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">KLettres 培训课程</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">KLettres 訓練階段</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/klettres/klettres.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>klettres</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="21.08.0" date="2021-08-12"/>
    <release version="21.04.3" date="2021-07-08"/>
    <release version="21.04.2" date="2021-06-10"/>
    <release version="21.04.1" date="2021-05-13"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
